Sketch the first open rail on the ground
Start sketch on picked face or ground
Pick empty ground to start sketch
Line tool — click start and end points
Line — first point
Line — second point
Commit sketch and show yellow pad
Sketch a second open leg that meets the rail end
Start sketch on picked face or ground
Pick empty ground to start sketch
Line tool — click start and end points
Line — first point
Line — second point
Commit sketch and show yellow pad
Ctrl+click both cyan pads, then Merge Join
Add sketch pad to selection
Merge join — connect pad endpoints into a path
Sketch a circle profile, then Sweep along path
Start sketch on picked face or ground
Pick empty ground to start sketch
Circle tool — click center, then radius
Circle — center
Circle — radius
Commit sketch and show yellow pad
Add sketch pad to selection
Sweep profile along path
Solid path sweep — 377 mm³